<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>San Juan del Sur and Tola</title>
    <description>Our mission at Trinity Real Estate is to be your best resource for San Juan del Sur real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Trinity Real Estate, your professional San Juan del Sur Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 13:53:19 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 13:53:19 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Assessing the San Juan del Sur Rental Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cmL3kmsK_Cw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Laura Taylor-Johnson joins me today to share her take on the San Juan del Sur rental market.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How’s the rental market in San Juan del Sur? To answer that question, I’ve invited Laura Taylor-Johnson, the head of Selva Pacifica, to join me for today’s video. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally from Canada, Laura has been coming down to Nicaragua for 12 years—the last 10 of them to build her thriving luxury rental business. Additionally, she was recently named the top Airbnb host in the country by Airbnb, Inc., and she’s currently working with them to increase the visibility of Nicaragua to potential travelers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does Selva Pacifica do? When Laura started collecting homes for rent 10 years ago, she realized there was no dedicated concierge service in the area. That’s how Selva Pacifica was born, and they assist property owners with their rentals. As indicated above, they work specifically with higher-end homes in amazing locations. &lt;strong&gt;Not only do they work with the owners to ensure they get the best guests, but they work with the travelers to ensure they get the best houses.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=What will differentiate you is the quality of your home.%20http://localhost:4000/assessing-the-san-juan-del-sur-rental-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“What will differentiate you is the quality of your home.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of that, they handle all the advertising and marketing for their properties, and they have a team dedicated to showing guests the best side of San Juan del Sur. When guests leave, they follow up with them so owners have plenty of five-star reviews to help the exposure and profitability of their investments. They currently have 506 five-star reviews under their belt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Laura says that the rental market started slowly at the beginning of last year, but after that, we saw a progressive increase in tourists and home rentals. Last quarter, occupancy averaged over 60% in most of Selva Pacifica’s homes. A lot of their homes not only covered their costs, but they made a nice profit heading into 2020. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about buying a luxury rental (or you already own one that hasn’t been very successful), Laura’s first piece of advice is to &lt;strong&gt;reach out to a professional to help you.&lt;/strong&gt; Starting off in a saturated market like San Juan del Sur won’t be easy if you don’t have a professional by your side. If you contact Selva Pacifica, they’ll visit your home and discuss your goals with you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With so many rental homes in the market, &lt;strong&gt;she also advises differentiating your home.&lt;/strong&gt; Every rental in San Juan del Sur has a view; that won’t differentiate you in this market. What &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt; differentiate you is the quality of your home. You need to make sure it’s well-maintained and evokes your personal style. If you have a nice house with a view but don’t put any love and care into it, you won’t see a return on your investment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for Laura, you can email her at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:selvapacifica@icloud.com&quot;&gt;selvapacifica@icloud.com&lt;/a&gt;. If you’d like to know more about Selva Pacifica, feel free to visit their website selvapacifica.com. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any real estate questions, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I’d love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 16:37:50 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/assessing-the-san-juan-del-sur-rental-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/assessing-the-san-juan-del-sur-rental-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Gorgeous Home with a Gorgeous View</title>
        <description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_42AnC_Txq8?start=90&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The most impressive thing about this exclusive San Juan del Sur home isn’t the home itself. It’s the view.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we’re showing you one of our exclusive properties here in San Juan del Sur. Although this is a gorgeous four bedroom, four bathroom, nearly-500 sq. meter property, the most impressive thing about it is its breathtaking view of San Juan del Sur. To see a firsthand tour of this gorgeous property, watch our latest video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 15:07:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-gorgeous-home-with-a-gorgeous-view.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-gorgeous-home-with-a-gorgeous-view.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Special Holiday Message From Our Family to Yours</title>
        <description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/pI9oXfX9laU?start=127&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;In light of the holiday season, we want to share what we’re thankful for.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christmas is here, which means now is the time for gratitude. Here at Trinity Real Estate, we’re very grateful. &lt;strong&gt;2019 was a difficult year in Nicaragua, but we have many blessings for which we’re grateful.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, we added three great people to our team: Nancy, Gary, and Daphnee. We want to give a special thanks to them for joining us. We’re also grateful for all the families and investors who let us serve them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Here at Trinity Real Estate, we’re very grateful.%20http://localhost:4000/a-special-holiday-message-from-our-family-to-yours.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Here at Trinity Real Estate, we’re very grateful.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a personal note, I’m grateful for my family. Every time I come home, they’re waiting for me with their arms open, ready to support me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also grateful we fulfilled our promise of donating 10% of our sales volume to various institutions who need our help. For example, we were able to donate an important sum to San Juan del Sur Day School so they could award scholarships to kids in San Juan del Sur and help them get a better education. We also helped a young professional earn their master’s degree. Additionally, we were able to help the Catholic Church, which is very important to us. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lastly, I want to thank you for your support.&lt;/strong&gt; If you have any real estate questions or there’s anything my team and I can help you with, don’t hesitate to give us a call. From our family to yours, &lt;em&gt;Feliz Navidad&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 11:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-special-holiday-message-from-our-family-to-yours.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-special-holiday-message-from-our-family-to-yours.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Luxury at Its Finest</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jZ55bvVpqrE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’re looking to buy or rent a luxury home, I know just the place: Malibu in Pacific Marlin.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m spotlighting the exclusive Malibu properties in Pacific Marlin in San Juan del Sur. Joining me is the properties’ developer, Lance Rader of Malibu Developments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lance relocated to Nicaragua about 10 years ago, and his main business is building social housing in Managua. According to him, the Malibu development originally started as a vacation home for himself. He looked at several different locations along the Pacific Coast before choosing San Juan del Sur to start building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I was looking for a place to build a modern home to the standards that I’m used to building and US standards,” he says. “That’s how Malibu came about. I found a fantastic tract of land overlooking the ocean—about 30 stories up—and that’s where Malibu is now.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Every house comes fully furnished with top-of-the-line appliances and every item renters need.%20http://localhost:4000/luxury-at-its-finest.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Every house comes fully furnished with top-of-the-line appliances and every item renters need.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are three different products inside Malibu:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Single-family homes between 3,000 and 4,000 square feet featuring three and four bedrooms with infinity pools overlooking the ocean&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A 3-bedroom/3-bath duplex—also with an infinity pool overlooking the ocean&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3-bedroom/3-bathroom townhomes about 2,000 square feet with a valley view and community pool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Malibu also offers a great rental management program&lt;/strong&gt; which most of the property owners put their homes through. They have on-site management and staff to take care of the properties, and they advertise heavily for them—their occupancy rate is as high as 80%, depending on the time of year. Every house comes fully furnished with top-of-the-line appliances and every item renters need. Their furniture is of the high-end, contemporary style, and they both build it locally and import it from the US. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s Lance’s favorite part of San Juan del Sur? The same reasons he picked this spot to build in the first place: the beaches, weather, and fantastic nightlife. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to know more about these properties or you have any other real estate needs, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check out our featured listings in Malibu:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kwnicaragua.com/listingDetails/1082-169&quot;&gt;Duplex House in Malibu: 3 bed, 3 bath&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kwnicaragua.com/listingDetails/1082-200&quot;&gt;Townhouse in Malibu: 3 bed, 3 bath&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kwnicaragua.com/listingDetails/1082-636&quot;&gt;Exclusive Residence in Malibu: 4 bed, 4 bath&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kwnicaragua.com/listingDetails/1082-903&quot;&gt;Luxury House in Malibu: 4 bed, 4 bath&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 14:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/luxury-at-its-finest.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/luxury-at-its-finest.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I Send My Kids to San Juan del Sur Day School</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/07mdf5Ot-3o?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today I’m interviewing the founder and principal of San Juan del Sur Day School to show you why it’s such a great place to send your children.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m interviewing Julie Speier, the founder and principal of the San Juan del Sur Day School. Why? Because every time I tell someone I moved San Juan del Sur, they ask what I do about schooling for my children. This school has allowed us to live here and know our kids are receiving a great education. If you want additional information about the school, you can visit their website &lt;a href=&quot;https://sanjuandelsurdayschool.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:00: Introduction to today’s topic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:35: Introducing Julie Spire, founder and principal of San Juan del Sur Day School&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;0:55: How the school got its start&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:05: Statistics about the students at the school&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:00: About the teachers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3:40: The teaching philosophy at the school&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:25: The future for San Juan del Sur Day School&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:05: Wrapping up today’s topic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We love sending our children to the San Juan del Sur Day School, and I hope you learned a little more about it today. If you have any questions about real estate, please give me a call or send me an email. I would love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 09:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-i-send-my-kids-to-san-juan-del-sur-day-school.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/why-i-send-my-kids-to-san-juan-del-sur-day-school.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>10 Reasons to Love Life in San Juan del Sur</title>
        <description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/U7YGc1YgGyA?start=237&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today, I’m joined by a special guest, Veronica—my wife—to share 10 reasons why we love to live in San Juan del Sur.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife, Veronica, and I love living in San Juan del Sur. Here are the top 10 reasons why we do and why you might as well:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Family time.&lt;/strong&gt; San Juan del Sur is a small town that’s very inviting for families, and the beach isn’t far away.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wellness.&lt;/strong&gt; If you’re into healthy living, you’ll love San Juan del Sur—there are plenty of opportunities to do yoga, and fresh, healthy fruits and superfoods are readily available.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Surfing.&lt;/strong&gt; We are blessed to live near so many great beaches like El Remanso, Hermosa, Yankee, Maderas, and more. There’s great wind and surf almost all year-round.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schools.&lt;/strong&gt; The kids can attend San Juan del Sur Day School, which is a great place for them to be themselves, get in tune with nature, and learn and have fun at the same time.
&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=With the ocean on one side and beautiful trees on the other, San Juan is a great place to soak in the environment.%20http://localhost:4000/10-reasons-to-love-life-in-san-juan-del-sur.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“With the ocean on one side and beautiful trees on the other, San Juan is a great place to soak in the environment.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beach time.&lt;/strong&gt; The beach is pretty much in our backyard. Playa El Majahual is our favorite—there’s a lot of room for the kids to play and there aren’t usually many people around.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meeting new people.&lt;/strong&gt; We love meeting new people who travel to San Juan for vacation or who live nearby. They always have a story to tell.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Small town treats.&lt;/strong&gt; There’s little to no traffic or stoplights, and there are plenty of delicious foods made by the local people like coconut bread, picos, juices, and other organic treats.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Affordability.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s very cheap to live in Nicaragua, and San Juan is even cheaper.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enjoying the view.&lt;/strong&gt; We like to stay home sometimes, and there’s no better place to do that than in an affordable home with a fantastic view.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Immersion in nature.&lt;/strong&gt; With the ocean on one side and beautiful trees on the other, San Juan is a great place to soak in the environment. Monkeys and other animals can be seen frequently, and at night, the stars aren’t dimmed by city lights.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, there are plenty of reasons to enjoy life in San Juan del Sur. If you have any questions for us, don’t hesitate to reach out. We’d be glad to share any information with you that we can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 10:28:09 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/10-reasons-to-love-life-in-san-juan-del-sur.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/10-reasons-to-love-life-in-san-juan-del-sur.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How is the State of the San Juan Del Sur Real Estate Market?</title>
        <description>&lt;center&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/w4sNyCgdUXs?start=150&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Although our country is going through some tough times, our real estate market remains quite active. Here are some of the latest trends.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nicaragua is going through some tough, uncertain times right now, but it doesn’t mean that our real estate market has been inactive. &lt;strong&gt;On the contrary, it’s been quite active.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some sellers who have been willing to reduce their prices have been able to sell their properties. We’re definitely in a buyer’s market, but &lt;strong&gt;there aren’t a ton of buyers out there, so sometimes a price reduction is necessary to get a possible deal done.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeing a mix of lot, house, and condo purchases. None of these are more popular than the others. As long as the prices are in accordance to the level of risk the investor who purchases the real estate is taking, the chance of selling increases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We’re seeing a mix of lot, house, and condo purchases.%20http://localhost:4000/how-is-the-state-of-the-san-juan-del-sur-real-estate-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We’re seeing a mix of lot, house, and condo purchases.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rental market has been pretty active as well. &lt;strong&gt;Most investors have had to lower their rents in order to increase occupancy and cover costs, while some have been able to see positive cash flow numbers.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for me about the real estate market or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 09:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-is-the-state-of-the-san-juan-del-sur-real-estate-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-is-the-state-of-the-san-juan-del-sur-real-estate-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to My Website</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Friends and Clients, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you know, Nicaragua is rife with scenic views, gorgeous beaches, and luxurious properties from which native residents and travelers alike can enjoy all the country has to offer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In San Juan del Sur, in particular, there is no shortage of things to do.&lt;/strong&gt; Whether you’re looking to surf, lie out on the beach, or take advantage of the city’s more urban activities, San Juan del Sur has something for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There’s so much going on in our area, in fact, that I’ve decided to start showcasing these local attractions in the form of a video blog.&lt;/strong&gt; I plan to send you between two to three messages each month, each highlighting a different unique aspect of the San Juan del Sur and Tola areas so that you can gain a better understanding of what makes life here so special. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It has been a pleasure and privilege to have made a career out of helping connect people like you with the experiences living in these areas can offer.&lt;/strong&gt; As always, I would be happy to connect you with one of the many fabulous properties available here in Tola or San Juan Del Sur. Whether you’re looking to enjoy a vacation, retire, or explore whatever else the next chapter in your life may hold, I am always here to help you reach your goals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all of that said, I hope to hear from you soon. If you have any other questions or would like more information, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to connecting with you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your Realtor, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joao Mucciolo&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-website.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-website.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
