<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>San Juan del Sur Real Estate Podcast with Joao Mucciolo</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Trinity Real Estate - your professional San Juan del Sur Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Joao Mucciolo</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-12-12 11:24:47 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Joao Mucciolo</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Juan del Sur, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Joao@trinityrealestatenicaragua.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Joao Mucciolo</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Joao Mucciolo</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Juan del Sur, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the San Juan del Sur Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Trinity Real Estate - your professional San Juan del Sur Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I Send My Kids to San Juan del Sur Day School</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-i-send-my-kids-to-san-juan-del-sur-day-school.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joao Mucciolo</author>
        <pubDate>2019-11-26 09:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/School+Video.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m interviewing the founder and principal of San Juan del Sur Day School to show you why it’s such a great place to send your children.

Today I’m interviewing Julie Speier, the founder and principal of the San Juan del Sur Day School. Why? Because every time I tell someone I moved San Juan del Sur, they ask what I do about schooling for my children. This school has allowed us to live here and know our kids are receiving a great education. If you want additional information about the school, you can visit their website here.

Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to various points in the video. Feel free to watch the full message or use these timestamps to browse specific topics at your leisure: 

0:00: Introduction to today’s topic

0:35: Introducing Julie Spire, founder and principal of San Juan del Sur Day School

0:55: How the school got its start

2:05: Statistics about the students at the school

3:00: About the teachers

3:40: The teaching philosophy at the school

5:25: The future for San Juan del Sur Day School

6:05: Wrapping up today’s topic

We love sending our children to the San Juan del Sur Day School, and I hope you learned a little more about it today. If you have any questions about real estate, please give me a call or send me an email. I would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/School+Video.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/School+Video.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’m interviewing the founder and principal of San Juan del Sur Day School to show you why it’s such a great place to send your children.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joao Mucciolo</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’m interviewing the founder and principal of San Juan del Sur Day School to show you why it’s such a great place to send your children.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Juan del Sur, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>10 Reasons to Love Life in San Juan del Sur</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/10-reasons-to-love-life-in-san-juan-del-sur.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Joao Mucciolo</author>
        <pubDate>2019-11-12 10:28:09 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/10+razones+que+nos+gusta+vivir+en+San+Juan+del+sur.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today, I’m joined by a special guest, Veronica—my wife—to share 10 reasons why we love to live in San Juan del Sur.

My wife, Veronica, and I love living in San Juan del Sur. Here are the top 10 reasons why we do and why you might as well:


  Family time. San Juan del Sur is a small town that’s very inviting for families, and the beach isn’t far away.
  Wellness. If you’re into healthy living, you’ll love San Juan del Sur—there are plenty of opportunities to do yoga, and fresh, healthy fruits and superfoods are readily available.
  Surfing. We are blessed to live near so many great beaches like El Remanso, Hermosa, Yankee, Maderas, and more. There’s great wind and surf almost all year-round.
  Schools. The kids can attend San Juan del Sur Day School, which is a great place for them to be themselves, get in tune with nature, and learn and have fun at the same time.
“With the ocean on one side and beautiful trees on the other, San Juan is a great place to soak in the environment.”
  Beach time. The beach is pretty much in our backyard. Playa El Majahual is our favorite—there’s a lot of room for the kids to play and there aren’t usually many people around.
  Meeting new people. We love meeting new people who travel to San Juan for vacation or who live nearby. They always have a story to tell.
  Small town treats. There’s little to no traffic or stoplights, and there are plenty of delicious foods made by the local people like coconut bread, picos, juices, and other organic treats.
  Affordability. It’s very cheap to live in Nicaragua, and San Juan is even cheaper.
  Enjoying the view. We like to stay home sometimes, and there’s no better place to do that than in an affordable home with a fantastic view.
  Immersion in nature. With the ocean on one side and beautiful trees on the other, San Juan is a great place to soak in the environment. Monkeys and other animals can be seen frequently, and at night, the stars aren’t dimmed by city lights.


As you can see, there are plenty of reasons to enjoy life in San Juan del Sur. If you have any questions for us, don’t hesitate to reach out. We’d be glad to share any information with you that we can.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/10+razones+que+nos+gusta+vivir+en+San+Juan+del+sur.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/10+razones+que+nos+gusta+vivir+en+San+Juan+del+sur.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today, I’m joined by a special guest, Veronica—my wife—to share 10 reasons why we love to live in San Juan del Sur.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joao Mucciolo</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today, I’m joined by a special guest, Veronica—my wife—to share 10 reasons why we love to live in San Juan del Sur.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Juan del Sur, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How is the State of the San Juan Del Sur Real Estate Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-is-the-state-of-the-san-juan-del-sur-real-estate-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Joao Mucciolo</author>
        <pubDate>2019-10-28 09:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/Como+es+el+Estado+del+Mercado+Bienes+Raices+de+San+Juan+del+Sur_+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

Although our country is going through some tough times, our real estate market remains quite active. Here are some of the latest trends.

Nicaragua is going through some tough, uncertain times right now, but it doesn’t mean that our real estate market has been inactive. On the contrary, it’s been quite active.

Some sellers who have been willing to reduce their prices have been able to sell their properties. We’re definitely in a buyer’s market, but there aren’t a ton of buyers out there, so sometimes a price reduction is necessary to get a possible deal done.

We are seeing a mix of lot, house, and condo purchases. None of these are more popular than the others. As long as the prices are in accordance to the level of risk the investor who purchases the real estate is taking, the chance of selling increases.

“We’re seeing a mix of lot, house, and condo purchases.”

The rental market has been pretty active as well. Most investors have had to lower their rents in order to increase occupancy and cover costs, while some have been able to see positive cash flow numbers.

If you have any questions for me about the real estate market or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/Como+es+el+Estado+del+Mercado+Bienes+Raices+de+San+Juan+del+Sur_+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Joao+Mucciolo/Como+es+el+Estado+del+Mercado+Bienes+Raices+de+San+Juan+del+Sur_+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Although our country is going through some tough times, our real estate market remains quite active. Here are some of the latest trends.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joao Mucciolo</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Although our country is going through some tough times, our real estate market remains quite active. Here are some of the latest trends.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Juan del Sur, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to My Website</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-website.html</link>
        
        <author>Joao Mucciolo</author>
        <pubDate>2019-10-22 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>Friends and Clients, 

As you know, Nicaragua is rife with scenic views, gorgeous beaches, and luxurious properties from which native residents and travelers alike can enjoy all the country has to offer. 

In San Juan del Sur, in particular, there is no shortage of things to do. Whether you’re looking to surf, lie out on the beach, or take advantage of the city’s more urban activities, San Juan del Sur has something for everyone.

There’s so much going on in our area, in fact, that I’ve decided to start showcasing these local attractions in the form of a video blog. I plan to send you between two to three messages each month, each highlighting a different unique aspect of the San Juan del Sur and Tola areas so that you can gain a better understanding of what makes life here so special. 

It has been a pleasure and privilege to have made a career out of helping connect people like you with the experiences living in these areas can offer. As always, I would be happy to connect you with one of the many fabulous properties available here in Tola or San Juan Del Sur. Whether you’re looking to enjoy a vacation, retire, or explore whatever else the next chapter in your life may hold, I am always here to help you reach your goals. 

With all of that said, I hope to hear from you soon. If you have any other questions or would like more information, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to connecting with you soon!

Your Realtor, 

Joao Mucciolo
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>In addition to serving as your trusted real estate advisor, it is also my goal to serve as your resource for all things related to Tola and San Juan Del Sur.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Joao Mucciolo</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>In addition to serving as your trusted real estate advisor, it is also my goal to serve as your resource for all things related to Tola and San Juan Del Sur.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Juan del Sur, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Joao Mucciolo</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Joao Mucciolo</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Trinity Real Estate - your professional San Juan del Sur Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
